I've seen some really dumb commentary lately and it like literally makes me sad it it it literally
like there is fantasy and there is reality watching people say things like y'all acting like
this isn't about comedy y'all this is always how comedy has been if I go back in time you can't go
back in time you see that's the thing is that you can't you can't go back in time and when I see
the effort that people are trying to apply to this Kevin Hart roast it by the way is the exact
effort that folks try to apply to Kamala Harris it's just a constant rationalizing of ignorance
I I don't understand how you can expect to to get anywhere like you there is there is no self
reflection there's there isn't even any cohesive reflection what do you try to compare
1901 to 2026 nothing nothing is the same it's literally as if you don't grasp that if I start
cutting myself with a knife right here and I keep cutting myself with this knife for 40 years
I'm gonna cut my arm off the the the the cutting doesn't restart every four years
like what type of idiot what type of idiot what type of idiot are are you surrounded by or are you
existing as if you think that having a a roast for a black man that welcomes a
mega comic and presents a bunch of jokes that are low hanging racist jokes
in an environment that is loud they said what you want and what the masses want are different yes
because the masses are controlled and it is always those of us who are not that end up saving the masses
ass from being completely obliterated into oblivion
why the fuck am i following the masses are the masses
investigative curious no because the masses have all including a me
been under a psychological operation you determine what is
valid that's not it about the roast idea that people cannot grasp the reality
of their own existence and it is deeply frustrating for those of us who exist only in reality and
shelly shells 1107 said it right here there weren't any holocaust jokes not even like it was on bet
you know so i just want y'all to always remember that i'm always gonna stand 10 toes down i'm always
gonna be the same real one at all times i very rarely need y'all to check me because i will be the
first to check my motherfucking self and anybody that you see trying to make any kind of space for this
being acceptable is a coom period the the comics the black comics i see trying to say shit like well there
were black comics and you need to try to check me i really wish you wouldn't
i really wish you wouldn't i was able to leave stand up because i have many many other gifts beyond
just doing stand up and one of those gifts is i'm super duper fucking smart so i really wish y'all would
not attempt to insult my intelligence it doesn't matter if there are black writers and that writers
or white writers in that writers room if the outcome is incredibly denigrative and furthermore
uplifting of narratives that we continue to see weaponized against us in real ways
but this is the same type of shit that people thought about dave chappelle and his transphobic
content and then he had the nerve to turn around and say well i didn't know they was gonna do that with
it can anybody get beyond themselves i just i'm just wondering does anybody and yet are we gonna
hold people accountable for being so completely self-absorbed that they cannot see the reverberation
of the work they're doing even though their whole goal is for their work to reverberate
that's the whole goal mega comic did a great job gave him a standing ovation of himself
you all don't understand so much of this because you've only existed as an audience i have existed
in both leading that you grow spines because these these folks will not they will not loud mouths and
brittle spines i blocked mrs lashes because you know fuck her i'm gonna tell you something when i started
doing stand up you know part of the process of stand up is you know you got to go through different
phases and i started doing open mics and the open mics were all white boys who were not funny
they were racist and they were sexist they didn't have jokes they just had insults they were basic
and now to to attempt to be told that that same level of content is thank you the renee berry for
buying a badge thank you meraja for buying a badge i appreciate the love to be told that that level of
content is is something that is worthy of applause don't let these people fucking lie to you don't let
these comics that have lost sight of quality lie to you they have the nerve to compare that shit to
richard prior what and just so we're clear that's none of a lot of that shit don't hold up anymore
go try go try and watch delirious go try and watch delirious eddie murphy delirious you tell me if you
still think it's funny the same way that if you go and listen to the chronic you go and tell me if you
can still get through it you know better you do better that's the only reason we're here
that is the only reason we're here do you understand that that's the only reason we are guests we are
guests everything everything on this planet figures out how to evolve to continue to grow
and and we're now at a point where we're just evolving to continue to to like make money and
money is not even real so i i just i i want to acknowledge those of us who are not dumb
and who are not stagnant and who are not paralyzed by status who are not par who are not in who are not
in stasis by status who are not paralyzed um by a desire for popularity and some will say you think
we're better you think you're better than me yes i do i absolutely think i'm better than you i know
i'm better than you because my criteria for better is literally am i doing everything in my power
to be as useful to my community to this earth am i doing everything in my power to to do to be that
yes every day i'm better at it some days than others nothing is stopping you from being like me
the better that i refer to is um is accessible to everyone so uh i wish you all a great day
and a great mind and a great heart my album truth translator is coming out june 14th
i hope you will the music will be available for any price you want to pay um and the music does what
i believe that the comedy should do what i believe the films should do and what i believe the books
this should do it fertilizes and fortifies us
you